Okay, I can do this
Just go for it!
The important
thing is
to create a friendly
vibe where
he'll naturally give
you his number
A compliment
works the best
But don't overdo it
Compliments should
sound natural
For example
something
about his looks?
Thanks for
lending me this
Wow, Hyeon-wu
You look even more
handsome right now
Maybe it's because
you're tall
Shut the hell up
But I'm serious…
Was that wrong?
He's really
playing hard to get
A compliment
alone won't do
Here's the
second method
Lower his guard
with a simple snack
You can also touch
him this way
Hey, Lee Hyeon-wu
Ta-da!
What are you doing
crazy b******!
I'm not
going with you
So that's the guy
I'm sorry, Il-tak
What I told you
wasn't for
exchanging numbers
It's the secret to
flirting with a guy
I can't stand other
girls around you
The women next to
my brother
Because I can't
accept it